You ever just sit somewhere and watch
people for a minute? You can tell the
ones walking by that are just [__]
tired. Tired of the bills, the kids, the
spouse, the job. I like to refer to them
as the walking dead. [music] I was one
of those people for a long, long time. I
think there was about a 3-year period
where I was just going [music] through
the motions. When you're doing it, it's
normal. And everybody else feels like
that, too.
Nothing's wrong. You just keep doing the
next right thing. You know, I was paying
for gas on my credit card, making $18 an
hour at a family medicine clinic during
COVID. Something Something flipped. I
made my own garden. I started building
weird [__] in the backyard, and stuff
that the neighbors looked at like there
was involved. The [music] kids were
coming home telling me [__] that they
learned at school from their friends. My
dream job. I had the idea that I wanted
to help people in a real way. The health
care system was was what I sought out.
And when I got in there, it became very
clear that there is no profit in cure.
None of it was right. And I think a lot
of people that reach out to us have that
same feeling. None of [music] this is
right, and they want out. Therein lies
the problem. I also wanted out. But for
3 years, I sat there and I made excuse
after excuse. [music]
I don't have enough money. How am I
going to do this on my own? I have these
bills. I can't pull the kids out of
school. It finally clicked. I was just
making up excuses because I was scared
of change. [music] I wanted everything
to feel better, but I didn't want the
discomfort that was going to come with
change. It's not fun. It's not
comfortable. It is terrifying. It can be
the littlest shift, but as soon as that
littlest shift starts, it's a snowball
effect. And then suddenly, you're
selling your house. You're kicking your
husband out. You're quitting your job.
You're pulling your kids out of school.
You're buying a $2,000 school bus, and
you're on your way. [music] I didn't
have a shitload of money. I didn't have
all the answers. I knew what needed to
happen. I had no idea how to get there,
but I knew I had to start. Nothing
changes until you stop trying to make it
feel better, and you decide you are no
longer staying [music] in it.